[
  {
     "category":"Geography",
     "id":"622a1c387cc59eab6f950802",
     "correctAnswer":"North America",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "South America",
        "Oceania",
        "Europe"
     ],
     "question":"The country of Dominica is on which continent?",
     "tags":[
        "geography"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"medium",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Science",
     "id":"622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951037",
     "correctAnswer":"Shoulder blade",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "Ribs",
        "Collar Bone",
        "Kneecap"
     ],
     "question":"What is the common name for the scapula?",
     "tags":[
        "science"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"medium",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Society & Culture",
     "id":"622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcc7",
     "correctAnswer":"Afroasiatic",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "Kra–Dai",
        "Niger–Congo",
        "Austronesian"
     ],
     "question":"The language 'Sudanese Arabic' belongs to which language family?",
     "tags":[
        "language",
        "society_and_culture"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"hard",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Geography",
     "id":"6237359acfe13103f55eb54b",
     "correctAnswer":"Niger",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "New Zealand",
        "Nepal",
        "Netherlands"
     ],
     "question":"Which region of the world uses '.ne' at the end of its web addresses?",
     "tags":[
        "the_internet",
        "geography"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"hard",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Arts & Literature",
     "id":"622a1c397cc59eab6f950e82",
     "correctAnswer":"Robert Louis Stevenson",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "Oscar Wilde",
        "Agatha Christie",
        "Joseph Conrad"
     ],
     "question":"Which author wrote 'Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde'?",
     "tags":[
        "arts_and_literature"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"hard",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Food & Drink",
     "id":"625007240d86c8f685d80f17",
     "correctAnswer":"Ziti",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "Macaroni",
        "Penne",
        "Tagliatelle"
     ],
     "question":"Which pasta's name means 'Bride and bridegroom'?",
     "tags":[
        "food",
        "words",
        "language",
        "food_and_drink"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"hard",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Arts & Literature",
     "id":"622a1c397cc59eab6f950e11",
     "correctAnswer":"Dan Brown",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "Stephen King",
        "Donna Leon",
        "Frederik Pohl"
     ],
     "question":"Which author wrote 'Angels & Demons'?",
     "tags":[
        "literature",
        "arts_and_literature"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"medium",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Geography",
     "id":"626030cc4b176d54800e3d3f",
     "correctAnswer":"Cameroon",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "Algeria",
        "Mauritius",
        "Tunisia"
     ],
     "question":"Where would you find the city of Douala?",
     "tags":[
        "cities",
        "africa",
        "geography"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"hard",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Society & Culture",
     "id":"62ab33065202de619af28138",
     "correctAnswer":"Focus",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "2CV",
        "XK120",
        "Corolla"
     ],
     "question":"Which of these is a model of car made by Ford?",
     "tags":[
        "motoring",
        "business",
        "society_and_culture"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"medium",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  },
  {
     "category":"Science",
     "id":"622a1c3e7cc59eab6f952315",
     "correctAnswer":"The Jurassic Period",
     "incorrectAnswers":[
        "The Thoracic Period",
        "The Mezozoic Period",
        "The Triambic Period"
     ],
     "question":"Which Period Came Between The Triassic & Cretaceous Periods?",
     "tags":[
        "geology",
        "science"
     ],
     "type":"Multiple Choice",
     "difficulty":"hard",
     "regions":[
        
     ]
  }
]